[
  {
    "source":"mp3/AllSaints.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "All Saints",
    "choice2": "Cheeky Girls",
    "choice3": "Girls Aloud",
    "choice4": "Pussycat Dolls",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Beyonce.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Destinys Child",
    "choice2": "Beyonc√©",
    "choice3": "Rihanna",
    "choice4": "Nicki Minaj",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Shakira.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Christina Aguilera",
    "choice2": "Katy Perry",
    "choice3": "Shakira",
    "choice4": "Taylor Swift",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/ChemicalBrothers.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Daft Punk",
    "choice2": "Moby",
    "choice3": "Faithless",
    "choice4": "The Chemical Brothers",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/GrooveArmada.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Underworld",
    "choice2": "Groove Armada",
    "choice3": "Roger Sanchez",
    "choice4": "Haddaway",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/RobbieWilliams.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Seal",
    "choice2": "Justin Timberlake",
    "choice3": "Robbie Williams",
    "choice4": "Keane",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Supergrass.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "The Verve",
    "choice2": "Manic Street Preachers",
    "choice3": "Pulp",
    "choice4": "Supergrass",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Whigfield.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Whigfield",
    "choice2": "Bassment Jaxx",
    "choice3": "Faithless",
    "choice4": "Alice Deejay",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/SirMixAlot.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "MC Hammer",
    "choice2": "Sir Mix-a-Lot",
    "choice3": "Rick James",
    "choice4": "Busta Rhymes",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/WyclefJean.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "will.i.am",
    "choice2": "Fugees",
    "choice3": "Wyclef Jean",
    "choice4": "Pras",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/TheWhiteStripes.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "The Lumineers",
    "choice2": "The Rasmus",
    "choice3": "The Killers",
    "choice4": "The White Stripes",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/KaiserChiefs.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Kaiser Chiefs",
    "choice2": "Franz Ferdinand",
    "choice3": "Kings of Leon",
    "choice4": "Arctic Monkeys",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/KoolAndTheGang.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "KC and The Sunshine Band",
    "choice2": "Kool & The Gang",
    "choice3": "Boney M",
    "choice4": "Earth, Wind & Fire",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/A-Ha.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Dire Straits",
    "choice2": "Rick Astley",
    "choice3": "A-Ha",
    "choice4": "Bronski Beat",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/SaltNPepper.mp3",
    "question": "Who singings this song?",
    "choice1": "Naughty By Nature",
    "choice2": "TLC",
    "choice3": "S'Express",
    "choice4": "Salt N Pepper",
    "answer": 4
  }
]